A Guide to the League of Women Voters of Virginia records, 1920-2011
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Local Leagues., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 60-69)
  - Subseries 1: Individual Local Leagues, 9 boxes (Box 60-68)
    - Hampton-Newport News: A Citizen's Guide to Newport News, Virginia (2 copies) and Newport News, Virginia: City Government. (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Hampton-Newport News: yearbook and members handbook. (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Hampton-Newport News: correspondence, 1992, 1994. (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Hampton-Newport News: disbandment, 1997. (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Hampton-Newport News: needlepoint. (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Loudoun County: bylaws, 2005. (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Loudoun County: bulletins, May 1993, January/February, April 1996. (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Loudoun County: Know Your County (2 copies) and Know Your Schools. (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Loudoun County: study--Land and Community. (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Loudoun County: correspondence and papers, 1991, 1993. (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Louisa County: by-laws. (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Louisa County: annual report, 1981. (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Louisa County: board meeting minutes and annual meeting minutes, 1979-1985 (board minutes), 1982 (annual meeting minutes). (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Louisa County: bulletins, 1982-1984. (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Louisa County: correspondence, 1979-1985. (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Louisa County: Louisa: A County Study. (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Louisa County: board of directors directories and membership directories/rosters, 1980-1985. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Louisa County: budget information, 1980-1985. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Louisa County: brochures. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Louisa County: miscellaneous papers. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Lynchburg: Government of Lynchburg, voter's guide, and brochures, 1969, 1977, no date. (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Lynchburg: positions, budget, 1988-1989. (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Lynchburg: study. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Lynchburg: correspondence, 1991. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Lynchburg: map--districts and wards. (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Lynchburg: membership directories, 1990-1993. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Montgomery County: annual meeting minutes and invitation to 10th anniversary, 1981 (anniversary), 1993 (minutes). (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Montgomery County: A Citizen's Guide, Who's Who in Government, and Facts for Voters, 1976-1982, 1990-1991. (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Montgomery County: members handbook, 1976-1977. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Montgomery County: study, 1997-1998. (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Montgomery County: correspondence, 2004. (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - National Capital Area (inter-league organization): by-laws. (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - National Capital Area (inter-league organization): annual meetings, 1992-1993. (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - National Capital Area (inter-league organization): annual reports, 1975, 1977-1980, 1982-1984. (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - National Capital Area (inter-league organization): Who Makes the Decisions?, What's What in Metropolitan Washington, and brochures. (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - National Capital Area (inter-league organization): NCA Drug Study, June 1989. (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - National Capital Area (inter-league organization): position papers, 1978-1979, 1981, 1983, 1993, 2005. (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - National Capital Area (inter-league organization): annual Congress workshops, 1978, 1982-1983. (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - National Capital Area (inter-league organization): board directories and member directories, 1977[?]-1980, 1991. (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - National Capital Area (inter-league organization): miscellaneous papers. (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: by-laws. (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: name change. (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: annual meetings, 1988, 1991-1992. (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: board meeting minutes, 29 April 1992. (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: Guide to Norfolk City Government. (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: A Parent's Resource Guide to School-age Child Care in Norfolk(3 copies). (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: newsletter, June 1993. (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: correspondence, 1992. (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: Bill of Rights workshop and town meeting, 1991. (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Norfolk-Virginia Beach: membership information. (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): by-laws and policy. (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): non-partisan political policy. (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): newsletters, 1990-1992. (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): Voter's Bill of Rights and Take Back the System. (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): board and league metting announcements and minutes. (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): board papers. (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): treasurer's reports. (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): correspondence, 1988-1993. (Box 65, Folder 42)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): candidates forum and questionnaires. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): materials from the national office. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): sample of a citizen's guide from Dare County, North Carolina. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): materials for study (health, education). (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): membership rosters, 1990-1992, no date. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): clippings, 1990-1992. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): forms, surveys, photographs, etc. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Northern Neck (member-at-large): miscellaneous papers. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Portsmouth: founding, 1958-1960. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Portsmouth: annual reports, 1959-1964. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Portsmouth: minutes, 1960-1965. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Portsmouth: president, 1951-1963. (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Portsmouth: officers and membership, 1961-1965. (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Portsmouth: finances, 1958-1965. (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Portsmouth: correspondence, 1958-1963. (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Portsmouth: bulletins, 1964-1965. (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Portsmouth: state consultant committee, 1962-1965. (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Portsmouth: newsletters, 1958-1964. (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Portsmouth: decision to disband, 1964-1965. (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Portsmouth: A Guide to the Government of the City of Portsmouth. (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Prince William Area: by-laws. (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Prince William Area: organization and disbandment. (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Prince William Area: board meeting minutes and annual meetings, 1989-1992. (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Prince William Area: position papers. (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Prince William Area: Prince William: Citizen's Information Guide. (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Prince William Area: They Represent You, 2008. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Prince William Area: newsletters, January-June 1992. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Prince William Area: correspondence, 1989-1991. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Prince William Area: miscellaneous papers. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Richmond: by-laws. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Richmond: annual reports, 1986, 1989-1992. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Richmond: Recycling (one 1988 copy, two 1990 revised copies), Facts for Voters, and brochure. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Richmond: boundary reorganization. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Richmond: clippings. (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Richmond: miscellaneous papers. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Roanoke: papers, 1966, 1976-1977, 1989, 1991-1993. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Roanoke: disbandment, 1996. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Rockbridge Area: membership lists, newsletters, and position papers, 1986 (membership list and newsletter), 1988 (newsletters and position paper), 1990 (newsletters). (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Rockbridge Area: correspondence, 1985, 1992, 1994. (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Rockbridge Area: Directory of Area Officials, Facts for Voters, Know Your Rockbridge Area, and Twenty Years in Review. (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Rockbridge Area: revised by-laws, 1994. (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Rockbridge Area: disbandment, 1995. (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Rockbridge Area: disbandment, 1996. (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Southwest Virginia (Wise County-Norton): recognition paperwork. (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Southwest Virginia (Wise County-Norton): revised by-laws, 1994. (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Southwest Virginia (Wise County-Norton): correspondence, 1992-1993. (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Southwest Virginia (Wise County-Norton): correspondence, 1994-1996. (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Southwest Virginia (Wise County-Norton): disbandment, 1998-1999. (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Staunton: This Is Staunton. (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Waynesboro: annual meetings, 1985, 1992. (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Waynesboro: board meeting minutes, 1998. (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Waynesboro: Know Your City and map of Waynesboro. (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Waynesboro: Valley Voter, 1993, 1998. (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Waynesboro: correspondence and membership, 1993, 1998. (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Williamsburg-James City County: Citizen's Hornbook and Report of the Williamsburg Regional Commission on Growth. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Williamsburg-James City County: health care and mental health. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Williamsburg-James City County: papers, 1989, 1992-1993. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Williamsburg-James City County (York County): Who's Who in Government and papers. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Winchester-Frederick County: recognition papers, 1995. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Winchester-Frederick County: correspondence, 1994-1995. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Winchester-Frederick County: president's presentation, 1996. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Winchester-Frederick County: board minutes and newsletter, 1997. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Winchester-Frederick County: disbandment, 1996-1998. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Winchester-Frederick County: membership rosters. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 2: General Files, 2 boxes (Box 68-69)
    - Disbandment letters (Roanoke and Gloucester-Mathews) 5 July 1996. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Presidents, 1975. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Boards. (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Annual financial reports, 1958-1969. (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Annual financial reports, 1970-1975. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Annual financial reports, 1976-1981. (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - State presidents' letters and memos to local league presidents. (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Calendar for local leagues, 1985-1986. (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Program planning. (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - From Planning to Position. (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Prospective league inquiries, 1977, 1981-1986, 1992-1995. (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Organization institute, 3 June 1954. (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Consultant service for local leagues, 1961-1964. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Organization papers, 1975-1976, 1986-1987, 1993-1997, no date. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - A Guide to Organizing Leagues. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Handbook for Local League Leaders. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Training material for local program writing. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Local league highlights. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Self study for local leagues. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Easy Does It. (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Letters and publication samples (in-state and out). (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Local league forms (blank): action; budget; consultant report; priorities; request for help; self-evaluation; and withdrawal of recognition. (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Series VI: Publications., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 69-77)
  Publications contains brochures, booklets, newsletters, pamphlets, and reference materials produced by the League of Women Voters of Virginia, and include correspondence, receipts, and other papers relating to the writing, production and sale of these publications. Series also includes publications by the League of Women Voters of the United States and other organizations.
  - Subseries 1: The Virginia Voter, 3 boxes (Box 69-71)
    - Bulletin/The Virginia Voter, 1952-1959. (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1960. (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1961. (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1962. (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1963. (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1964. (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1965. (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1966. (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1967. (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1968. (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1969. (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1970. (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1971. (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1972. (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1973. (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1974 (1974-1975). (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1975. (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1976. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1977. (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1978. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1979. (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1980. (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1981. (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1982. (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1983. (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1984 (1984-1985). (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1985. (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1986 (1986-1987). (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1987. (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1988. (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1989. (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1990. (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1991. (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1992. (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1993. (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1994. (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1995. (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1996. (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1997. (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1998. (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - The Virginia Voter, 1999. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - The Virginia Voter, 2000 (2000-2001). (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - The Virginia Voter, 2001 (2001-2002). (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - The Virginia Voter, 2002. (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - The Virginia Voter, 2003. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - The Virginia Voter, 2004. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - The Virginia Voter, 2005. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - The Virginia Voter, 2006. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - The Virginia Voter, 2007. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - The Virginia Voter advertising, 1985-1990. (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - The Virginia Voter miscellaneous papers, 1974-1975, 1981, 1984, 1986-1987, 1995, 2000, no date. (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 2: Your Virginia State Government, 3 boxes (Box 71-73)
    - Your Virginia State Government, 1975. (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Your Virginia State Government (3 copies), 1978. (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Your Virginia State Government, 1980. (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Your Virginia State Government (2 copies), 1985. (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Your Virginia State Government teacher's guide, 1985. (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Your Virginia State Government, 1992. (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Your Virginia State Government, 1996. (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1973, 1975, 1978-1979. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1980-1982. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, January-July 1983. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, August 1983. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, September 1983. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, October 1983. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, November-December 1983. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, [1983-1984]. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1984. (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Your Virginia State Government C. F. Richardson Benevolent Foundation papers, 1984. (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1985. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1986. (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1987-1988. (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1989. (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1990-1991. (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1992. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1993. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 1995. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, 2005. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Your Virginia State Government papers, no date. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Your Virginia State Government brochures, 1983, 1985, 1992. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 3: Miscellaneous League of Women Voters of Virginia Publications, 2 boxes (Box 73-74)
    - Virginia Legislative Directory, 1972-1979. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Legislative Directory, 1980-1989. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Legislative Directory, 1990-1999. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Legislative Directory, 2000-2001, 2004-2009. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - A Visitor's Guide to the Virginia Legislature and papers, 1967-1981, 1998. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Newsletter, 1975, 1987-1988, 1992-1994. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Legislative Newsletter related papers, 1993-1994. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Legislative Priorities, 1996-1997. (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Divorce and Property Distribution: Equity in Virginia-a Woman's Perspective. (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Divorce and Property Distribution papers, 1984-1988. (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Divorce and Property Distribution papers, 1989-1991, no date. (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Vote in Virginia, 1968, 1972-1977. (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - The Role of the State in Local Finances. (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - The Role of the State in Local Finances part I. (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - The Role of the State in Local Finances part II. (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Taxes: Who Pays? Who Should? (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - School Finance News study kits I and II, 1980. (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - School Finance News related papers, 1980-1981. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - School Finance Study kit 1, 1992. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - State Financing of Elementary and Secondary Education and Virginia Town and City: Public Education. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 1954-1964-A Decade of Decision: Virginia Public Schools, 1954-1964. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Virginia's Water Supply Problems: Searching for Solutions, 1982. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Virginia's Water Supply: A Reference Handbook. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Handbook for Local League Leaders. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Membership: Tools of the Trade. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Membership: Tools of the Trade papers, 1981. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - You Hold the Key to Good Government. (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Annual report brochures, 1982-1986. (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Positions in brief brochures, 1987, 1989, 1994, 2004, 2005. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Citizens lobbying course and citizens planning project. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Elections and voting. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - League of Women Voters brochures. (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Voter information on 1976 constitutional amendment, 1976. (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - State bond issues flyer, 1977. (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Facts for Voters, 1978. (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Election guides, 1984-1985, 1989. (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Voters Guide, 2005. (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - The Balancing Act: Reapportionment and Redistricting. (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Brochures, miscellaneous. (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - State board of elections material. (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Examples of local league publications: Fairfax calendar. (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Examples of local league publications: We the People: A Guide to Government in Harrisonburg and Rockingham County. (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Examples of local league publications: A 20th Century Hornbook: A Guide to Modern Williamsburg/James City County. (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Examples of local league publications: The Government of Lynchburg. (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - Examples of local league publications: Know Your Schools (Loudoun County). (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Subseries 4: League of Women Voters of the United States Publications, 2 boxes (Box 74-75)
    - National Voter, 2003-2005. (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - National Voter, 2006-2009. (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Action. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - At Issue, Winter 1990-1991. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Close Up of Washington and Who Makes the Decisions [for Washington D.C.]. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Focus: UN and Economic Responsibilities and Questions and Answers on Economic Assistance to Foreign Countries. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - In Touch, Winter 1991. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Leader's Guide: The Federal Loyalty-Security Program. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Leadership for Effective Leagues. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Let's Have a Discussion. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Promoting Peace-Agenda for Change. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Publish Without Perishing. (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - The Role of Political Parties U.S.A., 1962. (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Significant Roll Calls. (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - One Man, One Vote (LWV-Cleveland, Ohio). (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous brochures. (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 5: General Publications, 2 boxes (Box 75-76)
    - Chesapeake Bay: Uses, Choices, and Conflicts. (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Conference on Appalachian Development. (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - A Legislator's Guide to State Tax and Spending Limits. (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Report of the Governor's Special Committee on Water Resources, Virginia Advisory Legislative Council to the Governor and the General Assembly. (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Election Laws, 1992. (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Candidacy Requirements for Certain Local Offices November 2003 Elections, 2003. (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Your Legal Rights as a Woman: A Handbook for Virginians. (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Newsletter of the University of Virginia Institute of Government, 1972, 1987-1988, 1990, 1992. (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - The Quarterly, 1988. (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Virginia State Legislative Guide, 2007-2008. (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Women (Virginia Council on the Status of Women), Spring 1988. (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Democratic Party of Virginia Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner: Right Now, 7 February 2004. (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Children's School Safety Book. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Capitol Connection, 1992. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - How Can I Vote in Virginia?, 1987. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Votes, 1990[?]. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - The Mini Page, 22 March 2009. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Women's Network Newsletter, October 1996. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous papers. (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 6: Reference books and Directories, 1 box (Box 76)
    - Reference books, 1980-1983. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Reference books and directories, 1983-1985. (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Reference books and directories, 1985-1986. (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Reference books and directories, 1986-1987. (Box 76, Folder 11)